National news network  How may I direct your call?
国家新闻传输网 请问转哪里?
There will be an explosion this morning
今天早上会有一场爆炸
Excuse me?
对不起?
I said,
我说了
"there will be an explosion this morning" A bomb
今天早上会有一次爆炸 一个炸弹
Oh,Sorry.Did you say A bomb,sir?
对不起 你是说炸弹?
-sir? -On a bus
- 先生? - 在一辆公共汽车上
in the city where it all began
就在那个一切开始的城市
Get my message out
把我的消息发出去
Message?
消息?
What message?
什么消息?
That this is only the beginning
这仅仅是开始
Until it is brought back under control,
如果不把它控制住
SEATTLE,WASHINGTON
西雅图 华盛顿
people will die
就会死人的
Hey! Mornin',JJ How was your
嗨! 早上好 JJ 你的…
weekend?
周末过得怎么样？
Yeah?
什么事?
Homeland security just reported a bomb threat for an unspecified urban area
国土安全部刚刚报告 某个未明区域受到炸弹恐吓
It was phoned into the national news network
国家新闻传输网接到了电话
I'll call you back
我会给你回电话
When?
什么时候?
Last half hour
半小时前
They need a threat assessment asap
他们需要尽快拿到威胁评估
-Get the team together -Yeah
- 把人马都集合过来 - 好的
Sorry
对不起
Did you say a bomb,sir?
你是说一个炸弹 先生?
On a bus in the city where it all began
在一辆公共汽车上 就在那个一切开始的城市
Get my message out
把我的消息发出去
Message?
消息?
What message?
什么消息?
That this is only the beginning
这仅仅是开始
Until it is brought back under control,
如果不把它控制住
people will die
就会死人的
In the last 20 minutes,
刚刚过去的20分钟里
virtually identical threats have been made to most of the coast-to-coast news networks in the country
类似的恐吓已经传遍了 全国的各大新闻网络
It's the same information just slightly different words
都是相同的信息 只有微小的差别
So it's not a recorded message or script
所以这不是一个录音留言或者一份手稿
Displays a measure of confidence
从中显示出了某种信心
He could have easily just called one network
他可以简单的只给一家传媒打电话
This guy obviously wants attention
这家伙显然是想要吸引注意
It's typical behavior for a personal cause bomber
典型的个人原因投弹行为
One bomb has a finite impact--
一个炸弹只有有限的影响
it's just a little package
只是一个小包裹
Make bunch of phone calls,that magnifies my explosion 100 times
打上一串电话 就可以使我的爆炸放大一百倍
We have the additional recorded calls being gathered for assessment
我们有更多搜集来的电话录音等待评估
Networks say the calls came from a restricted number
广播网称这些电话来自一个受限号码
2 have given limited permission to trap and trace the lines if we should need to
有两家提供了有限许可的线路 如果我们需要的话 可以诱捕和追踪
You got a news organization to agree to a trap and trace?
你能让一个新闻组织同意诱捕和追踪电话?
Who could say "no" to me?
谁能对我说不呢?
This is not likely al-qaeda.They don't call unless they bomb something
这可不象基地组织 他们炸完了才打电话
At homeland security's request,
国土安全部要求
the networks are going to keep this quite until we've assessed the situation
所有新闻网都保持沉默 直到我们对情况做出评估
It doesn't feel like a hoax
我觉得这不是恶作剧
His voice is calm,resigned
他的声音冷静 从容
He's made his decision.He's committed to it
他做了决定 就会坚决执行
Plus he said,
另外他说
"this is only the beginning"
“这仅仅是开始”
The beginning of what?And he also said,
什么的开始? 他还说
"until it is brought back under control" what's it?
“如果不把它控制住” 这是什么意思?
He has to call back
他一定会再打电话来
And if this threat isn't followed by an event,
如果恐吓之后没有一个事件发生
no one will take any future calls seriously
没人会把这种电话再当真了
So,
所以
we're going to tell the media to go ahead with the story?
我们要媒体继续这个故事?
Absolutely not
当然不
Threats like this with an unspecified location will just cause tremendous panic
此类未明区域的恐吓只会带来大面积的恐慌
Then
那么
what are we gonna do?
我们怎么办?
Unfortunately,all we can do is wait
不幸的是 我们只能等着
Seattle WASHINGTON
西雅图 华盛顿
Robespierre once wrote,
罗伯斯庇尔写道
"crime butchers innocents to secure a prize
罪恶屠杀无辜以保卫战利品
And innocence struggles with all its might
而无辜者尽其所能
against the attempts of crime"
与罪恶的企图抗争
So seattle's where it all began
那么西雅图就是一切开始的地方了
We just need to figure out what it is
我们只要搞清它是什么
And off the top of my head,
随便说的话
I can think of grunge music and overpriced coffee
我能想到的就是Grunge摇滚乐和超贵的咖啡
That doesn't seem significant enough for terrorism
对恐怖行动来说重要意义还不够
It's a personal cause bomber
这是一个个人原因投炸弹的人
It only needs to be of significance to him
只要对他来说够重要就行了
Agent nick casey,seattle field office
探员Nick Case 西雅图办事处
S.S.A.Hotchner How do you do?
SSA Hotchner 你好 (S.S.A:Supervisory Special Agent 高级特别侦探)
This is dr.Spencer reid,
这是Spencer Reid博士
S.S.A.Morgan,
SSA Morgan
agent jareau,and S.S.A.Gideon
Jareau探员 和 SSA Gideon
Have you identified the device?
你们确认装置了吗?
Looks like a small pipe bomb attached to an umbrella
看起来象是小型自制铁管炸弹 连在一把雨伞上的
I'd like to take a look at those bomb fragments as soon as possible
我想尽快看看炸弹碎片
I've got bomb squad experience
我有炸弹方面的经验
As soon as they're catalogued
等他们归好类就行
How many people were on the bus when the explosion went off?
爆炸时车上有多少人?
25 including the driver
加上司机有25个
Explosion killed 2--
其中两人死亡
the driver and a young male
司机和一名年轻男性
Injured 7
伤了7个
A pipe bomb on a crowded city bus and only 2 people are killed?
一个自制铁管炸弹在这么拥挤的城市 只造成两人死亡?
Had a relatively small charge
因为有个相对较小的范围
The 2 dead were found closest to the bomb at the time of detonation
两个死者在爆炸时离炸弹最近
Sylvia cohen,an elderly passenger,
Sylvia Conhen 一位年长的乘客
found the umbrella on the floor at her feet
发现雨伞在她脚边
She said the young man volunteered to take it to the driver for her
她说那个年轻人主动拿去交给了司机
She's pretty broken up about it
她因此非常不安
Have you vetted and debriefed the rest of the passengers?
你们已经调查和访问过其他乘客了吗?
I have their info if you want to talk to them
如果你想跟他们谈谈 我有他们的信息
Did you get their positions?
你有他们的位置吗?
Sorry?
对不起?
Where they were on the bus?
他们在车上都在什么位置?
No
没有
JJ,Maybe you can recontact the passengers and map their locations
JJ 你可以再联系一下这些乘客 画下他们的位置
Yeah,you got it
好的 就去
Nobody saw anyone leave the umbrella?
没人看到是谁留下的雨伞?
No
没有
But,you know,from the style it looks like,uh,
但是你看 从手法上来说象是
remote detonator on the corner over there
遥控引爆器 在那边角落里
You say remote?
你说遥控?
Limited frequency remote
窄频遥控
-Like a garage door opener? -**************************
- 类似开车库门的遥控器? - 差不多吧
That's awfully risky
那太冒险了
Anyone on this bus could have accidentally detonated the bomb just by pulling out of their garage
在这车上的任何人按一下开车门的遥控器 就会无意中引爆炸弹
He used a remote from the corner
他在一个角落使用这个遥控器
Did he want to be close enough to see what happened?
他是想近距离地看到发生了什么吗?
Or did he need to be mechanically?
还是设备的原因使他他必须如此?
Those remotes are pretty limited.He probably needed to be
这些遥控器的距离是很有限的 他可能不得不如此
Then he might have been nervous
那么他可能非常紧张
Maybe that made him stand ouT
这就使他很突出
I could set up a public service announcement encouraging anyone
我可以安排做一个公共服务声明
who was in the area of the time of the bombing to contact us
鼓励爆炸发生时在场的人联系我们
Well,we do need a press conference
好吧 我们的确需要开一个发布会
But it'll be about getting this unsub to call us
但这是为了使那个嫌犯打电话给我们
We're still trying to determine what happened
我们仍在试图澄清事件原委
Initial reports called it a bomb,
最初的报告称之为爆炸
but since no one has claimed responsibility,
但因无人宣称对此负责
we can't rule out some kind of mechanical failure
我们无法排除机械故障的可能
Supervisory special agent gideon
高级特别探员Gideon
will be handling any future communication on this incident
将负责处理此事进一步的信息
If anyone has any information they feel might be helpful,
如果任何人发现有用的信息
please contact S.S.A.Gideon at the number appearing on your screen
请打屏幕上的号码联系Gideon探员
We will keep you posted with future developments
我们会随时汇报进展情况
Thank yoU
谢谢
Think that was enough?
你认为这样就够了吗?
It will definitely stress him that his message isn't getting out
这绝对是向他强调了 他的消息还未被发出
What if he doesn't call?
如果他不打电话怎么办?
Reid and morgan are going over the device
Reid和Morgan在研究那个装置
Maybe they'll come up with something
也许他们会发现什么
You know,reid,
你看 Reid
the bomber could have bought this detonator at any old toy store
在任何老玩具商店都能买到这种引爆器
You take a remote control car,
你买个遥控小汽车
plane,boat,
飞机 船
attach a detonator like this to the motor,
把这个引爆器接到发动机上
touch the remote,
按一下遥控器
boom! Instant fourth of july
! 立刻就象到了国庆节
How you doing?
你好
I'm derek morgan
我是Derek Morgan
This is dr.Spencer reid We're with the B.A.U.
这是Spencer Reid博士 我们是BAU的
Sondra atkins Cass or cassy works,too
Sondra Atkins  Cass或Cassy也行
Bomb tech
炸弹结构
It's a really nice reconstruction
这个重建做的真不错
Oh,it wasn't that hard
这没多难
Explosive was limited and the fragments were comparatively easy to locate
爆炸是局限性的 碎片相对比较容易找到
Ok So tell me what else you got here?
那么告诉我们你还发现了什么?
Well,besides the light explosive load,he used dry peas
除了爆破荷载较轻 他还用了干豆
Dry peas
干豆
He chose a shrapnel that wouldn't do too much damage outside of a limited range Why?
他选择了榴散弹 那么在有效范围之外 不会造成太多损害 为什么?
What's he doing,trying to minimize his kills?
他想做什么 想把伤害降到最低?
It also has a picture enaved on it
这还刻了一副画
Right there It's robot with an arrow through it
是呀 一个箭头穿过一个机器人
Anti-robotics?
反机器人?
Doesn't the city center bus stop use smart buses?
市中心公共汽车站不是使用智能公交吗?
-Smart buses? -Yeah
- 智能公交? - 是的
Hi-tech buses that use time sensors on the buses
使用时间传感器的高科技公共汽车
and the bus stops to give out arrival and departure times?
然后车站给出到达和离站时间?
Yeah Went automated last year
是的 去年开始就自动化了
So he's anti-technology
那么他是反科技
Maybe
也许
Hey,dollface,
嗨 娃娃脸
ready to work some magic for me?
准备好给我变个戏法了吗?
Challenge me,
向我挑战吧
you beautiful,behavioral analyst
你这漂亮的行为分析家
Domestic terrorist activity in the seattle area
西雅图地区国内恐怖主义活动
Ugh,morgan,I said challenge me
呃 Morgan 我说的是挑战我
Doesn't even raise my blood pressure
可这都不能让我血压上升
Pacific northwest is,like,ripe with the disgruntled
太平洋西北部充满着不满情绪
You have animal rights,zoning laws
有动物权益 分区法律
Specifically anti-technology?
特别一点的 反科技?
Ahh,yes My looney opposites
啊 是的 发狂的反对者
Here's something!
有了!
Month ago Tacoma,washington--
一个月前华盛顿州塔科马
disguised young guy went crazy on a bunch of computers at a science lab,
一批伪装过的年轻人 对着一个实验室里的电脑发狂
screaming,
叫着
"we will soon be the slaves and the machines will be the masters" Yikes
我们很快就要成为奴隶 机器会成为主人 呀!
That would totally suck for me
这我可受不了
I'm surrounded in here
我在这里被机器包围着呢
Come on,what are you worried about?
好啦 你担心什么?
You got me to protect you
有我保护你呢
Ha! Now that gets my blood up
哈! 现在我血压升高了
I'm uploading the video to you now
我把视频上传给你
What else do you have,garcia?
还有什么 Garcia?
I also found an article in the st
我还在St Dennis大学校报上
Dennis university college newspaper
发现一篇文章
Last spring,
去年春天
close to the school,an internet cafe was attacked
在学校附近 一家网吧被袭击了
campus internet cafe bombing attributed to fft brgade
(电脑上的文字:校园网吧爆炸系FFT队所为) 有人制造了软盘炸弹并用在四台电脑上
No one was injured
没人受伤
Who uses floppy disks anymore?
谁还会用软盘呀?
Right,agent brain,that was the point of the attack
对 大脑探员 这就是此次袭击的重点所在
They left a note,
他们留了个条子
"ultimately,you'll be as obsolete as your graveyard technology"
最终 你们也会没用的 就象你们过时的技术
Is the note signed?
那条子有签名吗?
"F.F.T.Brigade" I'm finding references to a freedom from technology brigade,
FFT队 是指"反对科技"队
a fringe group that's showing up lately
一个新近出现的极端组织
Anything else in the note?
字条上还有什么?
Yeah
有的
There's A not very artistic drawing of what kind of looks like a robot with an arrow through it
有个不那么艺术的画 看起来象是一支箭穿过机器人
I'm uploading it to you now
我现在上传给你
You know,seattle's the birthplace
你知道 西雅图是
of some of the most cutting edge technology in the world
世界尖端技术的诞生地
Where it began
“开始的地方”
I think we're ready to give a profile
我认为我们现在知道个大概了
We believe the unsub resides in seattle
我们相信嫌犯住在西雅图
All of the attacks,most of which have just involved property damage,
所有的袭击--大部分仅造成财物的损坏
have taken place here,
就发生在这里
and the timing and location indicate knowledge of the area
时间和地点都显示出是这个地方
Even though he escalated to a lethal bombing today,
尽管目前他升级到了致命的炸弹
we don't believe that that was necessarily his intention
我们并不认为那是他的主要意图
In fact,anyone not directly next to the device received minor injuries
事实上 如果不是紧挨着那个装置 就不会造成大的伤害
So we think fear may have been the larger motive
所以我们认为恐惧是更重要的动机
So he's a terrorist then
那么他是个恐怖分子了
He is But
他是 但
that's too vague of a description for our purposes
但就我们的目的来说 这样的描述太含糊了
Douglas and olshaker categorize bombers as criminal,
Douglas和Loshaker把投炸弹的人归类为犯罪
group cause,psychologically disorganized,
团体原因 心理混乱
and personal cause bombers
以及个人原因
And we believe this guy to be a personal cause bomber
我们认为这个人属于个人原因投炸弹的人
And personal cause bombers are motivated by an underlying emotional conflict
个人原因投炸弹起因于潜在的情感冲突
In an interview from prison,
在一次监狱访谈中
the unabomber,ted kaczynksi,
那个独立投弹人 Ted Kaczynksi
admitted that while he was a graduate student at the university of michigan,
承认当他在密歇根州大学做研究生时
he started having fantasies of becoming a woman
开始幻想成为女人
Even got on a list to get a sex-change operation but,
甚至计划去做变性手术
during a mandatory psychological exam prior to the procedure,
手术程序前的一个强制性心理测验
he changed his mind
使他改变了主意
He told the psychologist that he made a mistake
他跟心理医生说他犯个了错
From that moment through the next 3 decades of his life,
自那一刻起 在他生命接下来的三十年中
ted kaczynksi carried out a campaign of isolation and murder
Ted Kaczynksi进行着孤立自己和谋杀的行动
This unsub is male
嫌犯为男性
He lives alone
独自生活
He's possibly self-employed
可能是自由职业者
He's highly organized
他非常有条理
He's meticulous
非常小心谨慎
And he's very smart
非常聪明
And he seems odd to those who know him
认识他的人都觉得他很古怪
Angry,distant,
易怒 冷漠
prone to sudden violent rage
容易突然狂燥而使用暴力
This is not the kind of guy whose neighbors will be surprised to find out what he's arrested for
可不是那种要是被捕了 邻居们会觉得大吃一惊的人
This guy's neighbors will have no trouble believing it
这家伙的邻居们不会觉得奇怪的
Targets appear to be technology,but
目标看来是有技术的 但
not the hi-tech variety
不是那种高科技类型的
The kind of technology we're surrounded by
而是我们周围到处都是的那种技术类型
In a city the size of seattle,we're talking 10,000 possible targets
象西雅图这种规模的城市 我们有大概一万个可能的目标
Agent gideon,you got a call on the tip line
Gideon探员 专线上有你的电话
Ok,
好
go ahead
开始吧
This is agent gideon
我是Gideon探员
Why did you say no one took responsibility?!
你为什么说没有人负责?
I'm sorry
对不起
We called them all--
我给他们都打过电话--
all the networks--
所有的广播网
before anything happened
在事发之前
They didn't tell anyone?!
他们没有说?!
Well,the networks are incompetent
这些广播网不能胜任
If you need to get your message out or you have a demand,
如果你想把消息送出去 或者你有什么要求
I'm in a much better position to do that for you
我比他们更能胜任
You have a name,sir?
你的名字 先生?
We're the F.F.T. Brigade
我们是FFT队
No No No I mean you specifically What
不 不 不 我是说你个人
what can I call ya?
我该叫你什么?
This is not about individuals
这不是个人行为
F.F.T.'S a major organization--
FFT是一个主要组织
we have hundreds of members
我们有一百多个成员
But you-- you have a name
但你--你有名字
You may call me allegro
你可以叫我Allegro
So,allegro,let's meet somewhere
那么Allegro 让我们见个面
We can talk about your message,uh,
谈谈你的消息 呃
try to help you--
试着帮助你
if the networks won't get our message out,
如果传播网不能送出我们的消息
then it is up to you
那就是你的事了
It's your responsibility
是你们的责任
So call this number
那就打这个号码
They'll put you through to me immediately
他们会立刻把你转到我这来
I won't need to call again
我不需要再打了
My message will be here when you arrive
等你到时 消息就在这里
I'm sorry,when I arrive?
对不起 当我到时?
What's that?
那是什么?
Allegro?
Allegro?
Hello?
喂?
Can you smell that?
你闻到了吗?
Same explosive,just more of it
同样的炸弹 只是量更大
Yeah.And same detonation device,too
爆炸装置也一样
The gas station closed 15 minutes prior to the explosion
爆炸前15分钟 加油站就关门了
Fortunately,
幸运的是
the worker had already gone home
工人已经回家
No casualties,an escalation in the size of the explosion,
没有伤亡 爆炸的大小升级了
and a decrease in the number of victims
而受害者的数量却减少
We need to do a grid search as soon as possible
我们得尽快进行网格搜索
What do I tell them we're looking for?
我们该说要寻找怎样的人?
Said his message would be here when we arrived
他说过 他的信息会在我们到的时候出现
Clear!
安全!
It's a book
是一本书
Says,"manifesto"
写着"宣言"
Bag it
包起来
His manifesto's main demand is completely unrealistic--
他在宣言中的要求简直不现实
stop all automated machinery that's replaced american workers within a week
在一周内 停止所有 替代工人的自动化机器
And if his demands aren't met,
如果不满足他的要求
he says he'll detonate even larger bombs
就会引爆更大的炸弹
So we have an anti-technology bomber who so far has attacked
我们面对的是一个反对科技的罪犯 至今为止攻击了...
computers,an automated cashier,
电脑 自动收银机
an automated gas station,
自动加油站
and a smart bus
还有一辆智能巴士
Who calls himself allegro
他自称Allegro
Wh--what was that?
什么?
He told me to call him allegro
他让我叫他Allegro
Of course
当然
yeah It's a book
这是一本书
Yeah It ought to be
很明显是的
No,no It's an actual book--
不 真的有这么一本书...
a novel I read it as a kid
我小时候读过的一本小说
It's called empty planet by one-hit-wonder author david hansberry
名字叫《无人星球》 David Hansberry的唯一作品
It's got it all-- technoids,minutians
里面什么有...Technoids Minutians
All that stuff's in there
无所不包
It's robots that take over the world once they figure out how to reproduce with humans
是关于机器人在懂得和人类繁殖后 统治地球的故事
Essentially,humanity's lost to technology
实质上就是人类输给了科技
And the hero of the book
小说的主人公
is a 12-year-old boy named allegro who builds an army and fights for the humans
是个叫Allegro的12岁小孩 他建立了军队 为人类而战
Morgan,have garcia get as much information as possible on the author of empty planet
Morgan 让Garcia查查那个作者 越详细越好
David hansberry?
David Hansberry?
Uh,hansberry,yeah
恩 Hansberry
I'm on it
好的
There was a passenger on the bus yesterday,
昨天巴士上有一名乘客
a dr.Emory cooke
Emory Cooke博士
He's supposed to be some kind of computer genius,
他好像是电脑天才
pioneer in artificial life
人工生命的先驱者
Yeah,cooke
是的 Cooke
He developed software that mirrors the human reproductive system
他开发的软件映射了人类繁殖系统
Computers that can replicate themselves
电脑就能自我复制
So maybe cooke was the target and not the smart bus
也许他的目标是Cooke 而不是巴士
If so,that would definitely be imitating events from the book
如果是这样的话 那一定是模仿书中的情节
Allegro and his army not only destroyed robots,
Allegro和他的军队不仅销毁机器人
but they assassinate the scientists that are responsible for creating them
还暗杀那些发明它们的科学家们
Dr.Cooke was sitting right in front of sylvia cohen
Cooke博士就坐在Sylvia Cohen前面
And the umbrella was initially found underneath dr.Cooke's seat
那把伞起初就在Cooke博士的座位下
Yeah
是的
Thank you for coming so quickly,dr.Cooke
感谢你这么快赶来 Cooke博士
People,particularly some religious fundamentalists,
某些人 尤其是那些宗教原教旨主义者
oppose the work you do
反对你的工作
Do you receive any threatening letters
你有收到过恐吓信
or phone calls from anyone about your work?
或是电话 威胁你的工作吗?
Never
没有
Really?
真的?
I've managed to put to rest
我能很好地解决
certain anxieties about the godlessness of
关于人工生命无神化的焦虑
artificial life by openly sharing my own personal beliefs
通过分享我的个人信仰
Which are?
是什么?
No scientific knowledge precludes the existence of god
任何科学知识都不能否定上帝的存在
There are also those with very strong ethical concerns
还有些强烈的道德问题
Ethical concerns revolve mainly around the manipulation of already-existing life forms
道德问题主要都是围绕 操纵现已存在的生命形式
My work is on creating artificial life,
我的工作是创造人工生命
which presents far less ethical dilemma
其中的道德博弈问题很少
Not from the man that put the bomb on the bus yesterday
没从昨天引爆巴士的人那里收到恐吓?
He seems to be obsessed with the science fiction novel
他似乎沉溺于那本科幻小说
by david hansberry called empty planet
David Hansberry写的《无人星球》
Are you familiar with the book?
你熟悉这本书吗?
I'm friends with the author
我和作者是好朋友
The author of the empty planet used david hansberry as a pseudonym
David Hansberry是他的笔名
Come on,garcia,I know you got his name,
说吧 Garcia 我知道你查到名字了
so give it up
别想忽悠我
Her name,
她的名字
you cute little chauvinist,
你这个可爱的大男子主义
is ursula kent,
她叫Ursula Kent
and she's a literature professor at
是个文学教授
oh,my
我的天
In seattle,st Dennis university
她在西雅图St.Dennis大学教书
Where the floppy disc bombs were set
软盘炸弹设置的地方
Uh-huh
恩哼
Oh,you are the light of my life,sweet lady
你简直是我生命之光 甜心
Íô!Íô!Íô!Íô!Íô!Íô!
(法语：亲爱的，我不一直都是吗？)
Drives me crazy when you talk that voulez coucher stuff to me
每次你说法语 都让我疯狂不已
Stop it
别说了
Ursula kent is a brilliant woman
Ursula Kent是个聪明的女人
She's a post-modernist literature professor
她是后现代文学教授
Every semester I give a guest lecture in her class
每学期我都给她的班级开嘉宾讲座
She--she's here?
她在这里吗?
In seattle?
在西雅图吗?
Is that not what I just said?
我刚刚没说清楚吗?
Sir,this guy reads empty planet like it's prophecy
先生 这个人以《无人星球》为预言书
He's targeting what he considers threats to the survival of human beings,
他的目标就是那些 他认为会威胁人类生存的人
and I believe that he finds you one of these threats,dr.Cooke
我认为你也是他目标之一 Cooke博士
As I've said,
我已经说过了
I rather doubt that
我宁愿不相信
Do you think the fact that
你在那辆巴士上
you were on that bus and you're friends with the author is a coincidence?
又是作者的朋友 你觉得这一切都是巧合?
A cognitive scientist at M.I.T. Once said,
麻省理工的一位认知科学家说过
"coincidences seem to be the source for some of our greatest irrationalities"
"巧合似乎是我们最大错误的根源"
Our minds see coincidences and--
我们大脑认为巧合...
I understood him
我明白他的话
I'd like to attach a protective detail for you,dr. Cooke,
我会安排人保护你 Cooke博士
until we find the guy
直到我们找到他为止
No Thank you
不用了 谢谢
-Excuse me? -Really,now
- 你说什么? - 真的 不用
Do I seem like the sort who would want to be
我看起来像是每天
followed around all day by a government goon squad?
都有个傻傻的政府保镖跟着的人吗?
I don't think so
我可不这么想
Goon squad?
傻傻的保镖?
Ever talk to someone who wants to continually show you he's smarter than you?
你有跟随时炫耀聪明比你的人 说过话吗?
Everyday
每天都有
I really hate that
我真讨厌这样
Garcia found the author of the book
Garcia发现小说的作者
David hansberry's just a pen name
David Hansberry只是个笔名
-The real name is ursula -ursula ken*
- 真名叫Ursula... - Ursula Ken
The professor of post-modern literature at
St.Dennis大学的后现代文学教授
st.Dennis university where the floppy disc bombs were sent
也就是软盘炸弹被送去的地方
Hmm.Anyway,JJ'S contacting her We can go see her any time
JJ正在联系 我们随时可以去见她
Let's go
走吧
We need to stop by a bookstore and get a copy of empty planet
我们得在书店停下 买本《无人星球》
I want to re-read before we talk to the author
在和作者对话前 我想再看看这本书
I haven't read it since I was 6.
上次看还是我6岁时候
6?
6岁?
I was still ridin' by big wheel at 6 years old
我6岁时还在玩摩天轮呢
Do you mind?It'll only take 10 minutes
可以吗? 只需10分钟
To buy it or read it?
买还是看?
Uh,both,actually
事实上 都是
Have agent casey set up protection for dr.Cooke
让Casey探员安排保护Cooke博士
Like him or not,he's in danger
不管他是否喜欢 他正处于危险之中
He used a compression detonator
他用了压力炸弹
Looks like it was under the seat
似乎是在座位下的
Once he sat down,it arms Detonated when he released the pressure by getting up
一旦他坐下后再站起来 便会释放压力 引爆炸弹
We wanted to make sure nothing went wrong this time
这次我们要确定没有任何错误
Nobody moved the umbrella
谁都别动"那把伞"
Hotch, gideon just talked to this guy
Gideon刚和这个人说过
Offered him security but he refused
要保护他 但他拒绝了
We were gonna set it up anyway
无论怎样 我们本准备安排的
I doubt it would have helped
也不一定就有用
What do you mean?
什么意思?
Compression detonator
压力炸弹
It had to have been set when he was with us or it would have detonated when he arrived at the field office
要给他安排保护 他就必须来我们这里 到时他一下车 炸弹也会爆炸
I'll get security to start running tapes of the lab for the last 2 hours
我让安全中心查查 过去2小时内的实验室录像带
Good
好
Gideon
Gideon
I'm glad no one but dr Cooke was hurt
我很高兴只有Cooke博士受伤
Dr Cooke wasn't hurt
他没有受伤
He was murdered
而是被谋杀了
Murder is not murder during war
在战争中 谋杀并不是杀人
But this-- this isn't a war You're--you're
但这不是战争 你...
you're livin' a novel , You're livin' a fiction
你活在小说中 活在虚幻中
- Will you meet my demands? - I can'T
- 你会答应我的要求吗? - 不可能
Stopping all automation at a week, you know that's impossible
在一周内停掉所有自动设备 你知道不可能的
And I want my manifesto printed in the seattle ledger by tonight
那在今晚之前 把我的宣言刊登在"西雅图分类报"上
Not the new york times, washington post?
不是纽约时报 华盛顿邮报吗?
Somebody in seattle important to you?
西雅图有什么人对你很重要吗?
There's more work to be done Much, much more
还有很多事要做 很多很多...
In fact, I'm going to visit an old acquaintance right now
事实上 我现在去见一个熟人
I'd invite you, but you're all going to be very busy
本想邀请你 但你将会很忙
Got it
拿到了
It was the last copy left, According to the clerk,
那员工说这是最后一本
it's actually become a pretty popular novel in science fiction circles
它在科幻小说中非常流行
Hotch
Hotch
A suspicious package was found at the water works
在水厂发现可疑包裹
The report says it looks like a pipe bomb, We're on our way there now
报告说看起来像管道炸弹 我们正在赶去
Ok, keep me posted
好 跟我保持联络
Unsub says we're gonna be busy
不明人物说我们将会很忙
Got it
好的
Looks like a pipe bomb at the water works
好像在水厂有个管道炸弹
Are we gonna go there?
现在要去那吗?
No, we'll still go see professor kent
不 还是去见Kent教授
Seatbelts
安全带
Hello Ursula kent
你好 我是Ursula Kent
Hi My pleasure, professor kent Jason gideon, FBI
很荣幸见到你 教授 我是Jason Gideon FBI
This is dr.Reid
这是Reid博士
It's a real pleasure to meet you I'm a fan of your work
很高兴认识你 我很喜欢你的书
Well,that's very nice of you to say
谢谢你这么说
Um, we can speak in my office
我们可以在办公室说
Lead the way
请带路
Your book has become a significant part of our investigation
你的书在我们调查中 是很重要的一部分
So your colleague explained
你们同事解释过了
I can't imagine how, though
但我还是不能想象
Bomber sees it as some kind of prophetic work
投炸弹的人把它视为预言书
He's attempting to save humanity by stopping the proliferation of robotic technology
他试图停止机器科技的发展 为了拯救人类
Well, that's absurd
太荒谬了
He's written a document-like manifesto called a guide to practical living,
他写了一本宣言 叫做"现实生活的向导"
and several sections of it are lifted directly from empty planet
里面许多部分都直接抄袭《无人星球》
He's taken up what he believes to be your cause
他自以为了解你写书的动机
and he's killing people for the sake of it
还为了它而杀人
But empty planet is a fantasy
但是《无人星球》只是幻想小说而已
Not to this man
对他来说不是
How could anyone think it's more than that?
怎么会有人这么想?
Unfortunately,it's impossible to predict how an unstable mind will interpret something
不幸的是 很难预测一个变幻莫测的人 会如何理解事物
And it's caused him to kill people?
这就让他去杀人了?
Do you know dr Emory cooke?
你认识Emory Cooke博士吗?
Very well
很熟悉
- He spoke to your classes? - Yes
- 你给你的班级开讲座? - 是的
Dr Cooke was murdered by the bomber an hour ago
Cooke博士刚在一小时前 被这个人炸死了
No
不会吧
clear!
安全!
It's safe now, Another small charge
现在安全了 又一个小炸弹
More meant to scare than to harm
只是想吓唬我们
Definitely the same unsub
绝对是同一个不明人物
Same signature
相同的标志
Casey
Casey
We'll get there ASAP
我们尽快赶到
There's another bomb at the post office
在邮局又发现了炸弹
Let's go
走吧
Professor, what is that?
教授 这是什么?
this is something someone--
这是某个...
a brilliant man gave me a long time ago before he died
睿智的人在他死前给我的 已经很久的事了
Actually, it's part of the inspiration for empty planet
事实上 这也启发了我写《无人星球》
James was a rather early alarmist about how much we were letting technology control our lives
James很早就开始担忧 科技会过多地控制我们的生活
It's become a sort of talisman for me
这已是我的护身符
You wear it when you teach?
你上课时也戴?
Sometimes, yes
有时是的
This has been etched on the bomber's devices
这被刻在嫌犯的装置上
Oh, my god
我的天
Bomber's written a manifesto he wants published,
嫌犯写了份宣言想要发表
but not in the national newspaper
但不是在全国性报纸
He wants it published in the seattle ledger
而是西雅图分类报
He wants someone here to read it
他想要这里的某个人看到
Have you ever had a student you think might be capable of doing something like this?
你曾教过可能会做这事的学生吗?
One of my students? Someone who hates technology ?
我的学生? 憎恨科技?
I'm a post-modernist
我是后现代主义者
In my area of study,technological inventions are often viewed as art objects
在我的学术范围 科技发明就像是艺术作品
That's true,but oftentimes the biggest critics of technology are those with scientific backgrounds,
话是没错 但有时最批判科技的 也是有着科学背景的人
and your students definitely fit that category
你的学生正符合这一特征
I need you to read this
你看看这个
Tell me if the writing seems at all familiar to you
看看字迹和写作手法是否熟悉
We'll wait
我们等着
Morgan
Morgan
Gideon, this guy's pissing me off right about now
Gideon 这个人把我惹疯了
This is the fourth location in the last 50 minutes
50分钟内已有4枚了
All of them have been very small bombs
都是些很小的炸弹
What kind of locations?
都在什么地方?
Municipal Water works,
西雅图市水厂
main post office,
中心邮局
social security office,
社会安保部
and now we're at the main branch of the library
现在是图书馆的主要馆区
Government buildings
政府大楼
Nothing involving technology
一点不包含科技？
No, nothin'
不 什么也没有
Then what's the purpose?
那是什么目的?
Distract us, keep us movin'
调动我们 让我们团团转
He's doing a damn good job, gideon,I don't like this at all
他干得真是该死得好 Gideon 我真是一点也不喜欢这样
We're chasin' this guy , We gotta do somethin' to get ahead of him
我们一直在追这家伙 一定要做些什么赶到他前头
Professor kent is reading the manifesto
Kent教授在看声明
I hope she reads as fast as reid
希望她看得能象Reid一样快
No one reads as fast as reid
没人能跟Reid比
- Is this the syllabus for your class? - Yes
- 这是你们课程的提纲吗? - 是的
Is it the same every semester?
每学期都一样吗?
Mostly, maybe a book or project changed
大部分是 也许换本书或一项研究计划
You only have 2 guest lecturers listed
你只列了两个客席讲座
Yes Uh,dr.Cooke and dr.Brasier
是的 呃 Cooke教授和Brasier教授
I always have those two, they're the only two I invite
我总是安排这两个 也只邀请这两个
They speak to every new class
他们为每个新班讲课
Dr.Cooke is-- was an expert on artificial life,
Cooke教授是--以前是人工生命的专家
- and dr.Brasier - artificial intelligence
- 而Brasier教授 - 人工智能
Dr.Brasier have an office on campus?
Brasier教授在校园有办公室吗?
No,
没有
it's cross town at rolling hills
穿过城镇 在Rolling山上
Morgan,I may have something
Morgan 我也许有发现
Hey,shelly
嘿 Shelly
I'm on my way to the symposium now
我现在在去座谈会的路上
Then save me a seat
那就给我留个位子
It's not rude
那不算无礼
Fine, then tell them
那好 就告诉他们
A VIP Is coming and you'll lose your job if you don't save the seat
有个VIP客人在来了 至于你 如果不帮我留座 我就炒了你
How long ago did her assistant say she left?
她助手说她是什么时候离开的?
- Minutes - Good,
- 几分钟前 - 好
maybe she's not in the car yet
也许还没有上车
shelly,I'm the VIP
Shelly 我是VIP客人
Yes, I am
是的 我是
- I don't care what you tell them - Stop the car!
- 我不管你怎么跟他们说 - 停车!
it`s long i can See, I'm tired and I need a seat
我有预感那要很长时间 我累了 想要个位子
ma'am! Stop the car!
女士! 停车!
Listen to me, Do not touch the ignition, Put the car in park
听我说 别碰点火装置 就停在停车场
Ma'am, put the car in park, don't touch the ignition
女士 车停这儿 别碰点火装置
Don't panic
别慌
- I'm FBI - FBI?!
- 我是FBI的 - FBI?!
- Are you dr.Brasier? - Yes, I'm dr.Brasier
- 是Brasier教授吗? - 是 我是Brasier教授
It's her Girl,
- 是她 - 姑娘
let me call you back
待会儿再打给你
Doctor,do not move
博士 别动
Excuse me?
什么?
I need you to sit as still as you can, please
请你尽量坐着不动
Damn it
该死的
doctor, listen carefully
博士 听仔细
You must sit as still as you posbly can, you understand?
你一定要尽全力坐着不动 明白吗?
Why?
为什么?
There is a bomb under your seat
座位下有一颗炸弹
Wait on the court
在法庭上等待
Be of good courage and he will strengthen thine heart
如果有足够的勇气 那将巩固你的心灵
Doctor
博士
you're gonna be just fine
你会没事的
He will strengthen thine heart
他会巩固你的心灵
Every device this guy has made has been fairly basic
这家伙使用的每个装置都是非常基本的
I'm guessing this is a simple lever action compression detonator
我猜这是一个低等级行动引爆压缩炸弹
Kinda like a door latch
有点像弹簧锁
I'm gonna use this,
我要用这个
put it between the latch and the seat bottom to depress the latch,
把它放在弹簧锁和座位底部之间 压紧弹簧锁
and I think we should be ok
我想那样就该没事了
- Should? - Well
- 应该? - 是啊
if there's mercury, we got problems
如果还有汞 那就有麻烦了
Thanks, hotchc
谢谢 Hotchc
Yeah, I'm right here
是 我就在这儿
So?
那怎么样?
Bomb tech's just about ready
拆弹组刚准备好
Maybe we should get over there
也许我们该过去那里
No, I think we would just be in the way
不 我想去了也是添麻烦
What about morgan?
Morgan怎么样?
He hasn't changed his mind
还是没改变他的想法
Morgan?
Morgan?
I'm ordering you to step away from the car
我命令你离开这辆车
Hotch, you know I respect you
Hotch 你知道我尊敬你
I'm not leavin' her
但我不会离开她
You should listen to your friends
你应该听你朋友的
don't do that
别这样
Don't you turn on me, doc
别突然放开我 博士
I'm right here With you
我就在这儿陪你
Got it?
明白了吗?
Ok
好的
My girl is using one of my hands
我的姑娘抓紧了我的一只手
Now, cassie
那么 Cassie
Yeah?
是?
You might the other one, so come on
你也许需要另外一只 快点
Do what you gotta do, let's do this
照你的计划做 行动吧
Step back
退后
Thank you
谢谢你
Aside from the sections of my novel that were blatantly plagiarized,
除了明显抄袭我小说的部分章节外
I didn't recognize anything
别的我都不认识
It's just page after page of the ravings of a lunatic
这只是一个疯子长篇累牍的胡话
Right now,a young man I greatly respect
现在 有一个我非常尊重和欣赏的年轻人
and admire is putting his life on the line because of that lunatic
就因为这个疯子让自己命悬一线
I'll look through it again
我再看一遍
Thank you
谢谢
You're gonna be just fine
你会没事的
Wait on the lord, I say
我要等候耶和华 我说
That was lucky
真幸运
Yeah, this one
是啊 这次
Yeah, they're ok
是的 他们没事
Good
很好
Now blow the car up
现在把车炸了
You're blowing it up?
你们要炸车?
Best way to keep dr Brasier safe is by letting the bomber think he was successful in Killing herc
让Brasier博士安全最好的办法 就是让投弹人以为这次已经成功地杀了她
Neighbors will hear an explosion, it'll be on the news
临近地区都会听见一声爆炸 也会出现在新闻里
You have a complicated life
你的生活很复杂
It's a complicated world
这是个复杂的世界
I'm sorry I couldn't be more help
很抱歉我没有帮更大的忙
Yeah, me,too
是呵 我也是
Give the manifesto a little more thought
再想想这份声明
Maybe something will occur to you without the pressure of us looming over you
也许少了我们在你身边的压迫感 能想到些什么
You could go back over your student list
你回头可以看看学生名单
Think about the males
想想那些男生
Anything odd about them
有什么奇怪的地方
Guy probably had a temper
那家伙很可能发过脾气
Somethin' you maybe haven't thought about for years
也许是你多年来都没有想到过的
I've have my T A Pull the files
我会让助教把档案找出来的
May I ask you something, ma'am?
能打听点事吗 女士?
Of course
当然
Why didn't you ever write another book?
为什么再也没有写书?
I guess it was the only story I needed to tell
我想那是我唯一需要讲的故事
I'll be working in my office most of the night,Don't hesitate to call
晚上我多半都会在办公室工作 有事尽管打电话
Thank you
谢谢
- Have a good night - you too
- 祝你晚上过得愉快 - 你也是
Melissa, I need you to pull the file and thesis paper on a student from last year
Melissa 我要你把去年 一个学生的档案和论文调出来
Yeah, his name is kenneth roberts
是的 他叫Kenneth Roberts
Great, thanks
很好 谢谢
So it begins with the father's suicide--
那么是从父亲自杀开始的--
Okay we got 5 crime scenes' worth of new information to go through
好的 我们要仔细检查 五个犯罪现场有价值的新信息
And the targets that unsub chose for the decoy bombs- do they force a change in the profile?
以及嫌疑人选择投放假弹的目标- 它们是否足以让我们改变设想方向？
I don't think so ,I think they are what the are
我不这么想 我觉得那些炸弹就是这个目的
Decoys to throw us off the trail of dr Brasier
诱使我们错过Brasier博士这条线索
Reid, what's that?
Reid 那是什么?
It's the subplot of the empty planet book
《无人星球》里的一段情节
Allegro kills his mother?
Allegro杀了他母亲?
Yeah, at the end,
是的 就在最后
he discovers he's adopted , He's reunited with his birth mom
他发现自己是被领养的 跟亲生母亲相认之后
He thanks her for having the strength to give him a better life,but,
他感激她有勇气给他更好的生活 但
ironically, he realizes that she herself has become a robot,
讽刺的是 他意识到 她已经自行变成了一个机器人
so he kills her
所以就杀了她
He sacrifices the one person in the world he has a biological connection with for the greater good
他将世上唯一与自己有血缘关系的人 作为祭品换取更好的货物
I thought we were talking about some geeky sci-fi book here
似乎我们讨论的是变态科幻小说
That sounds like greek tragedy
听起来象希腊悲剧
It's not played as a tragedy at all though
但并没有按照悲剧进行
In fact, his mother's incredibly proud of this final act,
事实上 他母亲对他最后的举动 表现出难以置信的自豪
like it's the ultimate fulfillment of his destiny,
这就像是他命中注定最终要履行的职责
proof that-- proof that she was right to have given him up in the first place
证明--证明她最初将他抛弃是正确的
Wait a minute, If he kills her, how do you know she was proud?
等一下 如果她被杀了 你怎么能知道她很自豪呢？
It's told from her point of view ,The whole book is
这是以她的视角讲述的 整本书都是
It's kind of like she's talking to the reader from heaven
有点像她在天国讲给读者听
Mother's the narrator
母亲是讲述者
Yeah it's really her story
是的 实际上是她的故事
Only story she needed to tell
她唯一要讲述的故事
And in order to fulfill the story, he's gotta kill his mother
为了符合故事 他要杀了自己的母亲
Don't hate the book
别讨厌这本书
Without this, I never would have known you at all
没有它 我根本不可能认识你
Mother
母亲
Kenneth,did you do this?
Kenneth 是你干的吗?
Did you kill dr Cooke?
是你杀了Cooke博士?
You've read my manifesto
你读过我的声明啦
Yes,and,uh,
是的 另外 呃
I thought some things seemed familiar
我觉得有些东西似乎很眼熟
And I know why you wrote empty planet
我知道你为何会写《无人星球》
I know what you've been trying to say
知道你一直想要说的是什么
Kenneth
Kenneth
You've misunderstood
你误会了
I don'T think so
我不这么想
Kenneth
Kenneth
the book is a work of fiction
这本书是一部科幻作品
- The book is a gift! - No,it isn'T
- 这本书是一份礼物! - 不是
It's just a story
只是一个故事
Then let me tell you a story, professor
那让我给你讲个故事 教授
My mother died when I was eight
八岁时我母亲过世
And then several years ago, my father needed a blood transfusion,
然后几年前父亲需要输血
and I tried to donate, only to discover that we had nothing genetically in common
我试图献血 却发现 我们在遗传上没有任何相同之处
I had to watch him wither away,
只得看着他渐渐死去
but before he died, he told me I was adopted
但他临死前 说我是领养的
This is not what you think
那并非是你想得那样
I needed to find my mother, but the records were sealed
我要找到我的母亲 但记录是保密的
All I knew was that I was adopted in youngstown,
只知道自己被领养的地点 在杨斯顿
ohio
俄亥俄州
And then I came across an article about professor ursula kent
后来碰巧读到 有关Ursula Kent教授的一篇文章
Favorite daughter of youngstown, famous writer of empty planet,
杨斯顿最爱的女儿 写无人行星的著名作家
and do you know, do you know,
你知道吗 知道吗
what that article said?
文章是怎么说的?
It--it said
它--它说
that you had given up a baby for adoption and that baby was the inspiration for the book
你曾将抛弃一个婴儿让人领养 而这本书的灵感就来源于这个孩子
That is true
那是真的
That is true ,But that is not the whole story
是真的 但不是事情的全部
When did you give up your baby for adoption?
你什么时候抛弃孩子给人领养的?
Wasn't it 26 years ago?
不是26年前吗?
In youngstown, ohio?
在俄亥俄州的杨斯顿?
Go GO !
走 走!
Kenneth, listen to me--
Kenneth 听我说--
no! It's your turn to listen
不! 该轮到你听了
Come on!
快点!
I came out here to take your class For a year,
我到这儿来上了你一年的课
I sat right there, Right there!
坐在那里 就坐在那里!
- And you never saw me! - If you'd just--
- 可你从来不看我! - 如果你只要--
- how could you not recognize me? - If you'd just come to me,
- 你怎么可能认不出我? - 你只要肯放开我
- I could've explained - then I realized,
- 我能解释的 - 后来我意识到
the only way to get you to see me was to live out the book ,But guess what?
唯一让你注意我的方法就是演出书中的故事 而你猜怎么着?
I did that And now,
我做到了 并且现在
you see me, don't you?
你注意到我了 对吗?
- This is our destiny! - Morgan, stairs, Go around
- 这是我们的命运! - Morgan 走楼梯 绕过去
the baby I gave up, it was a girl
我抛弃的那个婴儿 是个女孩儿
- It was a daughter - That's a lie
- 是我女儿 - 说谎
It was a girl
是个女孩儿
- That's a lie! - I'm so sorry
- 你在说谎! - 我很抱歉
- I know the pain you're in - why do you keep lying to me?!
- 我知道你内心的痛苦 - 为什么一直对我说谎?!
You're not my son!
你不是我儿子!
I promise I will do everything I can to help you find your birth
我保证会尽一切力量帮你找到亲生父母
- stop it! - Allegro!
- 别说了! - Allegro!
Wait
我有炸弹
Wait! Wait
等等! 等等
Don't want to hurt anyone
我们不想伤害任何人
You've gone to great lengths not to hurt anyone under unintentionally-
你已经竭尽全力不在无意下伤害任何人了
leave us alone!
让我们单独呆着!
No,we can't do that,allegro We cannot leave you alone
不 我们不能这么做 Allegro 不能让你们单独在一起
I'm ok Listen,
我没事 听着
I'm--I'm-- I'm ok
我--我--我没事
Doesn't have to end this way
不必弄成这种结局的
- This is how it ends! - You can change the ending--
- 这就是结局! - 你可以改变--
- this is how it ends! - How does it begin?
- 结局就是这样的! - 开始是怎么样的?
I don't even know the story ,Tell me the story
我甚至都不知道这个故事 跟我讲讲这个故事
You don't know the story!
你不知道整个故事!
I want to know, I'm in the story right now
我想知道 我现在就在故事当中了
Leave us alone!
让我们单独呆着!
Get an ambulance,get him out of here
叫救护车 带她出去
It's your shoulder
射中了你的肩膀
He's lost, He's just lost
他有点迷失自我 仅此而已
Just relax
放松一点
It'll be all right
会好的
Can't blame him
别怪他
Your eyes,ursula, I wanna see your eyes
张开眼睛 Ursula 我想看到你的眼睛
There they are. There you go
对，就是这样
- You listening? - I'm listening
- 你在听吗？ - 是的
He just wants to know who he is
他只是想知道自己是谁
That's all
只是如此
I understand
我理解
Open those eyes ,There you go
张开眼睛 就是这样
Right ,Keep looking at me
对 看着我
It's gonna be all right
一切都会好的
Just relax
只要放松就好
I'll be right back
马上回来
Do not cheat
不要作弊
JJ,A lot of science fiction's deeper than you might think
JJ 很多科幻小说比你想的要深奥
I mean,there are some genuine human emotions--
我指 有一些人类真实的感情--
yeah,let me save you the time, reid
行了 别浪费时间了 Reid
I am never going to comicon with you
我永远不会跟你一样的
- I... - gin
- 我... - 赢了
What,you don't trust me?
什么 你不相信我?
- come on - Let's just make sure
- 得了吧 - 只是确认一下
it's fun beating a genius
能打败天才真有趣
Genius dr Reid let you win
是天才Reid博士让你的
I hear you were worried about me
听说你很担心我
'Scuse me?
什么?
The bomb at the garage under the car?
车坐垫下的炸弹?
A young man that I greatly admire and respect is putting his life on the line
一个我非常欣赏和尊敬的年轻人 正冒着生命危险
What?
什么?
I do something?
我做了什么?
What you did with the bomb, stupid
你处理那颗炸弹的方式很愚蠢
Gideon,I couldn't leave that lady out there by herself like that
Gideon 我不能在那种情况下 让那女士一人呆着
I didn't say you were wrong
我没说你做错了
And what he said I said
而他所告诉你的我说过的那些话
I said
我是说了
I knew that
我知道